Sol Gorelick WAG 019
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- University of Michigan School of Social Work: Conference on Work Initiative Program (W.I.N. II) (Box 13, Folder 33)
- United Public Workers of America & United Public Workers (UPW and UPWOA) (Box 13, Folder 34)
- United WREP Workers Newsletter, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- U.S. Committee for a Democratic Spain (f/k/a U.S. Committe for a Carabanchel 10th), 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Veterans (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Veterans for Peace in Vietnam, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Vietnam War Activism, General (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Welfare Action Coalition (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Welfare and Health Council of New York City, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Welfare Brotherhood Committee, 1954; 1970 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Welfare and Job Rights Coalition (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Welfare Grant Increase Coalition, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Welfare Rights: Flyers, 1971; 1978 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Welfare Workers for Justice, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Welfare Workers for Peace, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Work Relief Employment Project: Manual for Public Agency Employees, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Workers Action Movement (Box 13, Folder 50)
- YM-YWHA: Various Branches, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- Youth Service League, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Conferences with Workers (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Client Advisory Committee Meetings: Minutes (Box 14, Folder 2)
- The City of New York Human Resources Administration, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Head Start (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Mobile Outreach Project, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Community Social Services (CSS): Recruitment Flyers (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Community Relations (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Human Resources Administration (HRA): Community Affairs Memo, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Relocation News; Department of Relocation (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Reorganization Plan for The City of New York Human Resources Administration (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Transit Strike (Box 14, Folder 11)
- United Jewish Appeal, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- What's on TV; Staff Meeting on the Air (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Taking on Welfare (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Appeal for Reduced Tutition Evening Courses (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Form M-289 and M-780; Application to Attend Serial Work Institute (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Application for Promotion (Box 14, Folder 17)
- College Tutition Refund: Forms, Memos (Box 14, Folder 18)
- American Public Welfare Association(APWA) Washington Report: Finance Committee Votes Workfare Substitute (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Form M96B: Application for Incentive Differential Based on College Credits or Associate Degree (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Forms: 340J's-287F's, ect. (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Loose, Unsorted Material (Box 15)
- Loose, Unsorted Material (Box 16)